Alphabetical Pamphlet Collection
University of Notre Dame Archives
- Alphabetical Pamphlet Collection: Printed Material, PALP
  - Inside Facts about the Catholic Church / by Coakley, Thomas F. DD, PALP 4/18
  - Meeting Houses or Churches / by Coakley, Thomas F. DD, PALP 4/19
  - Why I am a Catholic / by Coakley, Thomas F. DD, PALP 4/20
  - Social Effects of the Reformation / by Cobbett, William, 1929; PALP 4/21
  - Guy de Fontgalland - Angel of the Eucharist / by Code, Joseph B. Rev, 1932; PALP 4/22
  - Mother Seton - Foundress of Sisters of Charity in America / by Code, Joseph B. Rev., c1900; PALP 4/23
  - The Church and Christian Marriage / by Coghlan, Daniel DD, c1911; PALP 4/24
  - What is a Catholic? / by Cogley, John, 1953; PALP 4/25
  - Advertising the Faith Campaign the Knights of Columbus / by Comber, Thomas E. CSP, 1955; PALP 4/26
  - Catholic Art and Architecture / by Comes, John Theodore, 1920; PALP 4/27
  - Pray with the Church Holy Week / by Confraternity of Christian Doctrine, 1941; PALP 4/28
  - An American Teresa / by Conklin, Margaret M., 1947; PALP 4/29
  - Baptism / by Connell, Francis CSSR, 1930; PALP 4/30
  - Death Can be Joyous - The Sacrament of Extreme Unction / by Connell, Francis J., CSSR, 1940; PALP 4/31
  - Extreme Unction / by Connell, Francis Rev. CSSR., STD, 1938; PALP 4/32
  - Freedom of Worship the Catholic Position / by Connell, Francis J. CSSR STD, 1944; PALP 4/33
  - The Gift Divine - The Holy Eucharist / by Connell, Francis J., CSSR, 1939; PALP 4/34
  - May State forbid Marriage because of a Social Disease? / by Connell, Francis J. CSSR STD, 1938; PALP 4/35
  - Marriage / by Connell, Francis J. CSSR STD, 1940; PALP 4/36
  - Morality and Government / by Connell, Francis J. CSSR STD, 1949; PALP 4/37
  - The Power of the Holy Ghost: The Sacrament of Confirmation / by Connell, Francis J., CSSR, 1939; PALP 4/38
  - Questions Asked by Professional People / by Connell, F. J. CSSR STD LLD, 1960; PALP 4/39
  - The Sacraments What They Are. What They Do / by Connell, Francis J. CSSR, 1930; PALP 4/40
  - The Sacramentals What They Are. What They Do / by Connell, Francis J. CSSR STD, 1930; PALP 4/41
  - Shepherds of Christ's Flock - The Sacrament of Holy Orders / by Connell, Francis J. CSSR STD, 1940; PALP 4/42
  - The Seven Sacraments What They Are. What They Do / by Connell, Francis J. CSSR STD, 1939; PALP 4/43
  - Confidence in God / by Considine, Daniel SJ, PALP 4/44
  - Trust in God / by Considine, Daniel SJ, 1937; PALP 4/45
  - Converts Tell of Their Happiness / by Our Sunday Visitor Press, PALP 4/46
  - Birth Control / by Conway, Bertrand L. CSP, 1924; PALP 4/47
  - Can A Catholic Be President? / by Conway, B. L. CSP, 1928; PALP 4/48
  - The Catholic Evidence Movement / by Conway, Bertrand L. CSP, 1923; PALP 4/49
  - The Church and Eugenics / by Conway, Bertrand L., PALP 4/50
  - The Condemnation of Galileo / by Conway, Bertrand L. CSP, 1913; PALP 4/51
  - Confession of Sins a Divine Institution / by Conway, Bertrand L. CSP, PALP 4/52
  - The False Decretals / by Conway, Bertrand L. CSP, PALP 4/53
  - Is There A God? / by Conway, Bertrand L. CSP, PALP 4/54
  - Is There A True Religion? / by Conway, Bertrand L. CSP, PALP 4/55
  - The Question Box / by Conway, Bertrand L. CSP, 1929; PALP 4/56
  - Six Hundred Good Books / by Conway, Bertrand L. CSP, 1914; PALP 4/57
  - The Virgin Birth / by Conway, Bertrand L. CSP, 1924; PALP 4/58
  - Why Priests Do Not Marry / by Conway, Bertrand L. CSP, 1921; PALP 4/59
  - What They Ask About Divorce / by Conway, J. D. Monsignor, 1956; PALP 4/60
  - What They Ask About Engagement / by Conway, J. D. Monsignor, 1956; PALP 4/61
  - What They Ask About Keeping Company / by Conway, J. D. Monsignor, 1955; PALP 4/62
  - What They Ask About Love and Dating / by Conway, J. D. Monsignor, 1956; PALP 4/63
  - What They Ask About Marriage: Catholic and Non-Catholic / by Conway, J. D. Monsignor, 1956; PALP 4/64
  - What They Ask About Marriage Outside the Church / by Conway, J. D. Monsignor, 1955; PALP 4/65
  - What They Ask About Mixed Marriages / by Conway, J. D. Monsignor, 1956; PALP 4/66
  - What They Ask About The Rhythm / by Conway, J. D. Monsignor, 1956; PALP 4/67
  - Standing Room Only / by Conway, Pierre H. OP, 1946; PALP 4/68; Subject: Consideration of Angels' Intellect and Will
  - American Catholics a Household Divided? / by Coogan, John E. SJ, 1962; PALP 4/69
  - Rome and the American Labor Union / by Coogan, John E. SJ, c1962; PALP 4/70
  - Together at Mass: O Give Thanks to the Lord / by Coony, James F. - The Gregorian Institute of America, 1959; PALP 4/71
  - Primitive Man / by Cooper, John M., 1931; PALP 4/72; Subject: Religion and Morality in Primitive Culture
  - Gilds and Crafts of the Middle Ages / by Corbett, Aloysius ODC, PALP 4/73
  - The Church, The Constitution and Education / by Corbett, James A., 1950; PALP 4/74
  - Corpus Christi Carmelites - Home and Foreign Missioners - Brief Account of Their Origin, Life and Work, 1936; PALP 4/75
  - Corpus Christi Chronicle v. 6 No. 1 / by Church of Corpus Christi, 1940; PALP 4/76
  - The Christian In Action: Balancing the Family Budget / by Cort, John Mr. and Mrs., 1951; PALP 4/77
  - How to be a Practical Catholic / by Corrigan, D. J., 1956; PALP 4/78
  - How to Come Back to the Church / by Corrigan, D. J., 1957; PALP 4/79
  - How to Get Acquainted with the Catholic Church / by Corrigan, D. J. CSSR, 1956; PALP 4/80
  - Why it Pays to Be a Catholic / by Corrigan, D. J., 1956; PALP 4/81
  - Christ and His Church / by Corrigan, Joseph M. DD, 1931; PALP 4/82
  - Golden Jubilee Address / by Corrigan, Joseph M., 1940; PALP 4/83; Subject: The Catholic University of America
  - The Church and the Catacombs / by Costelloe, B. F. C., 1931; PALP 4/84
  - Lifting the Embargo - A Victory for the Vulture / by Coughlin, Chas. E. Rev, 1939; PALP 4/85
  - The Story of the Resurrection / by Coughlin, Chas. E. Rev, 1940; PALP 4/86
  - Why Leave Our Own? / by Goughlin, Chas. E., 1939; PALP 4/87
  - Mary in Islam / by Courtois, V. SJ, 1954; PALP 4/88
  - Courtship and Marriage - Practical Instructions By Priests of Society of Jesus / by The America Press, 1928; PALP 5/01
  - American Medicine American Morals and Birth Control / by Cox, Ignatius W. SJ, PALP 5/02
  - Birth Control, Birth Controllers and Perversion of Logic / by Cox, Ignatius W. SJ, 1936; PALP 5/03
  - The Divine Romance of Marriage / by Cox, Ignatius W. SJ, 1933; PALP 5/04
  - The Folly of Human Sterilization / by Cox, Ignatius W. SJ, PALP 5/05
  - Is Sexual Abstinence Harmful? / by Cox, Ignatius W. SJ, PALP 5/06
  - Mercy Killing is Murder / by Cox, Ignatius W. SJ, 1936; PALP 5/07
  - What Price Democracy? / by Cox, Ignatius W. SJ, 1939; PALP 5/08
  - Crisis of Christianity - A Statement of the Bishops of the US / by National Catholic Welfare Conference, 1941; PALP 5/09
  - One Fold One Shepherd - Pray that All May be One / by Cranny, Titus, Rev., 1954; PALP 5/10
  - The Name: Chair of Unity Octave / by Cranny, Titus Rev SA, c1954; PALP 5/11
  - Night Adoration in the Home Holy Hour / by Crawley-Boevey, Mateo SSCC, 1929; PALP 5/12
  - Holy Hour Book Five / by Crawley-Boevey, Mateo SSCC, 1943; PALP 5/13
  - Communism a World Menace / by Cronin, John F. SS, 1947; PALP 5/14
  - Prices in the United States / by Cronin, John F. SS, 1937; PALP 5/15
  - Rugged Individualism / by Cronin, John F. SS, 1937; PALP 5/16
  - Saint Raphael - Angel of the Sick / by Crumley, Thomas CSC, 1943; PALP 5/17
  - Expulsion of the Jesuits From Mexio / by Cuevas, Mariano SJ - Forrestal, Peter P., PALP 5/18
  - Catholic Responsibility in a Pluralistic Society / by Cummins, Richard J., 1961; PALP 5/19
  - National Federation of Catholic College Students, 1961; PALP 5/20; Subject: Constitution
  - The Gossipers / by Cunningham, Charles L., PALP 5/21
  - What is Life? / by Cunningham, James F. CSP, 1935; PALP 5/22
  - Catholic Education Catholic Foundation Plan / by Curley, Michael J. the Most Rev., PALP 5/23
  - The Hand of Pilate - Reply to Earl Browder's Message to Catholics / by Curran, Edward Lodge, PALP 5/24
  - Lent is Old Fashioned? / by Curran, Edward Lodge, 1933; PALP 5/25
  - Madness of Magdalen / by Curran, Edward Lodge, 1934; PALP 5/26
  - The Catholic Vocation in Journalism / by Cushing, Richard Cardinal, 1959; PALP 5/27
  - Permanent Industrial Peace - The Guide Posts of the Almighty / by Cushing, Richard J., 1946; PALP 5/28
  - Inter-Racial Justice / by Cushing, R. J. Most Rev., PALP 5/29
  - Postoral Letter - The Call of the Council / by Cushing, Richard Cardinal, 1962; PALP 5/30
  - The Church and Public Opinion - Pastoral Letter / by Cushing, Richard Cardinal, 1963; PALP 5/31
  - Moral Values and the American Society - Pastoral Letter / by Cushing, Richard Cardinal, 1961; PALP 5/32
  - The Way of the Cross / by Cushing, Richard J. DD, 1943; PALP 5/33
  - The Church and Reconstruction / by Cuthbert, Father OSFC, 1920; PALP 5/34
  - The Ethics of Labor / by Cuthbert OSFC, 1922; PALP 5/35
  - Socialism or Democracy / by Cuthbert OSFC, 1922; PALP 5/36
  - The Last World War / by Culligan, Emmett J., 1952; PALP 5/37
  - For Your Holy-Hour / by D., W., SSS, PALP 5/38
  - Holy Communion - The Frequent Communicant / by Dalgairns, John Bernard, 1926; PALP 5/39
  - Holy Communion In The Early Church / by Dalgairns, John Bernard, 1926; PALP 5/40
  - Church or Bible / by Damen, A. SJ, PALP 5/41
  - The Problem of Evil / by D'Arcy M. C. SJ, 1928; PALP 5/42
  - Can the Secular State Teach Religion? / by Dau, W. H. T., PALP 5/43
  - Speaking to Youth / by Davis, F. J. and George Stoll, 1946; PALP 5/44
  - Communism and the Masses / by Davoli, Joseph C., 1937; PALP 5/45
  - Christian Freedom / by Dawson, Christopher, PALP 5/46
  - Which Came First: Church or Bible? / by Day, Edward CSSR, 1960; PALP 5/47
  - Pitfalls of the Confessional - Confession, A Bugbear or a Boon? / by Day, Arthur SJ, 1934; PALP 5/48
  - Jews and Catholics / by Day, A. F. SJ, 1932; PALP 5/49
  - Defamers of the Church Their Character / by Our Sunday Visitor, PALP 5/50
  - Christmas Stories / by Dease, Alice, 1924; PALP 5/51
  - Catholic Family Life / by DeBlanc, Irving A. Msgr. Rt. Rev., PALP 5/52
  - Catholic Education in Mexico 1525 - 1912 - The Story of 300 Years of Constructive Endeavor / by Gerardo, Decorme, SJ, c1912; PALP 5/53
  - Common-Sense Talks on Morality / by Degen, Joseph, Rev, 1933; PALP 5/54
  - My Mind Wanders / by Delaney, John P. SJ, 1943; PALP 5/55
  - The Bandhura Tin Horn / by Delaunay, John B. CSC, PALP 5/56
  - Quadragesimo Anno in the Business World / by Harvard Business Review, 1932; PALP 5/57
  - To the Friends of the Cross / by De Montfort, St. Louis-Marie Grignion, 1947; PALP 5/58
  - The Secret of Mary / by De Montfort, St. Louis, 1950; PALP 5/59
  - Conversion of Russia / by Denissoff, Elie and Marie-Jacqueline, 1950; PALP 5/60
  - Wonder 7 Gifts / by Dennerle, George M., 1938; PALP 5/61
  - Teen Talks by a Teen Ager - No. 3 - On Decency / by DePrez, Norma, PALP 5/62
  - Teen Talks by a Teen Ager - No. 1 - On Dress / by DePrez, Norma, PALP 5/63
  - Meditations on the Cross and Passion / by De Sales, St. Francis, PALP 5/64
  - Our Children and the Mass - How to Make it ' live ' for them / by De Sauveboeuf, A. Rev., 1955; PALP 5/65
  - Holy Communion / by De Segur, Monsignor, 1915; PALP 5/66
  - The Key to The World's Progress / by Devas, Charles Stanton, 1908; PALP 5/67
  - Socialism / by Devas, Charles s. MA, 1905; PALP 5/68
  - The Book of Josue / by De Vault, Joseph J. SJ, 1960; PALP 5/69
  - Did Mary Have Other Children? / by DeVine, C. F. CSSR, 1946; PALP 5/70
  - Night Prayers on Calvary the Seven Last Words / by Diamond, Wilfrid, 1948; PALP 5/71
  - A Christmas Carol / by Dickens, Charles, 1922; PALP 6/01
  - The Easter Vigil / by Diekmann, Godfrey L. OSB, 1953; PALP 6/02
  - The Masses of Holy Week and the Easter Vigil / by Diekmann, Godfrey L. OSB, 1957; PALP 6/03
  - Need of an Organized Christian Force in the American Labor Movement / by Dietz, Peter E., PALP 6/04
  - People, Food, Space, and God The Population Explosion / by Dietz, Nicholas Jr., PhD., 1961; PALP 6/05
  - Tariffs and World Peace / by Divine, Thomas F. SJ and Economic Relations Committee - The Catholic Association for International Peace, 1933; PALP 6/06
  - The Bad Popes / by Doherty, J. E. CSSR, 1957; PALP 6/07
  - Harlem, Madonna / by Doherty, Eddie, 1944; PALP 6/08
  - Jehovah's Witnesses / by Doherty, J. E. CSSR, 1956; PALP 6/09
  - Revival Religion / by Doherty, J. E. CSSR, 1957; PALP 6/10
  - Are You Missing Something? / by Dolan, Albert H. O.Carm, 1940; PALP 6/11
  - Folan, Albert H. O.Carm / by Dolan, Albert H. O.Carm, 1945; PALP 6/12
  - The Gateway to Peace / by Dolan, 1938; PALP 6/13
  - Half Way to Happiness / by Dolan, Albert H. O.Carm, 1945; PALP 6/14
  - More Friends of Happiness / by Dolan, Albert H. O.Carm, 1945; PALP 6/15
  - Scapular Facts / by Dolan, Albert H. O.Carm, 1929; PALP 6/16
  - Scapular Facts - Handbook of Information About Our Lady's Scapular / by Dolan, Albert H. O.Carm, 1929; PALP 6/17
  - Novena For Vocations to the Religious Life of the Teaching Sisterhoods / by Dondanville, E. L., 1926; PALP 6/18
  - Horse and Mule Marriages vs Sacramental Achievement / by Donovan, Joseph P., 1949; PALP 6/19
  - Catholicizing the Family / by Donovan, Joseph P. CM JCD, 1945; PALP 6/20
  - Solving the Rural Problem in Missouri / by Donovan, Joseph P. CM, 1924; PALP 6/21
  - The World State Juridically More and Humanly Less Than League of Nations / by Donovan, CM JCD - The Catholic Association for International Peace, 1930; PALP 6/22
  - Are You Heeding Fatima? / by Dooley, Lester M, 1947; PALP 6/23
  - God's Guests of Tomorrow / by Dooley SVD, 1952; PALP 6/24
  - The Hidden Life / by Dooley L. SVD, PALP 6/25
  - The Mass in Your Life / by Dooley, L. M. SVD, 1954; PALP 6/26
  - I Witness a Baptism / by Dooley, L. M. SVD, PALP 6/27
  - Father Kapaun - The Ordeal of Chaplain Kapaun / by Dowe, Ray M., Jr. 1st - Lt. - Martin, Harold, 1954; PALP 6/28
  - The Breviary Office of the Feast of Christ as King / by Dowling, John Pius OP DD, 1931; PALP 6/29
  - Homage to Jesus Christ, King - The Proper of the Mass / by Dowling, John P. OP DD and Ellard, Gerald SJ, 1930; PALP 6/30; Central Bureau of the Central Verein
  - How to Make an Act of Perfect Contrition / by Dowling, Leo T. SJ, 1945; PALP 6/31
  - Race-Suicide Birth-Control / by Dowling, M. P., SJ, PALP 6/32
  - Personal Immortality / by Downey, Richard, DD, 1933; PALP 6/33
  - Catholics: Their Beliefs and Denials - The Church, the Bible and the Rule of Faith / by Downing, Nelius, 1925; PALP 6/34
  - The Home World Friendly Counsels for Home-Keeping Hearts / by Doyle, Francis X. SJ, 1922; PALP 6/35
  - Parish Holy Week Missal In Latin and English / by Doyle, Leonard J., 1956; PALP 6/36
  - Parish Holy Week Missal In Latin and English / by Doyle, Leonard J., 1960; PALP 6/37
  - Vocations / by Doyle, William SJ, 1914; PALP 6/38
  - Vocations / by Doyle, William SJ, 1931; PALP 6/39
  - Guide for Parents of Catholic Youth / by Driscoll, Justin A, 1958; PALP 6/40
  - Our Life of Grace / by Drummeg, Francis CSC, 1940; PALP 6/41
  - The Seven Last Words / by Duffy, T. Gavan Rev., PALP 6/42
  - The State and Catholic Education - High Importance of Religion and Schools Fostering It / by Duhig, James, the Most Rev., 1927; PALP 6/43
  - Polemic Chat / by Dunne, Edmund M., 1912; PALP 6/44
  - Religion and American Democracy / by Dunne, George H. SJ, 1949; PALP 6/45; Subject: Reply to Blanshard's American Freedom and Catholic Power
  - Christian Marriage / by Dupanloup Msgr, PALP 6/46
  - Refugees are People / by Dushnyck, Walter and William J. Gibbons SJ, 1947; PALP 6/47
  - History of Catholic Action in the United States / by Dwyer, Robert DD. the Most Reverend, 1954; PALP 6/48
  - The Kingdom of Promise - Scripture Textbooks for Catholic Schools / by Dyson, R. A. SJ and A. Jones, 1957; PALP 6/49
  - Mother and Helpmate of Christ / by Egan, James M. OP, 1952; PALP 6/50
  - Spirit World - A Consideration of the Angels / by Egan, James M. OP, 1946; PALP 6/51
  - The Redemption / by Ehmann, Benedict, 1941; PALP 6/52
  - The Conservation of Catholic Truth: An Example / by Elder, Benedict, 1923; PALP 6/53; With 1925/05/13 Letter - Callahan, P.H., to Robt. L. McWilliams
  - Follow the Mass / by Ellard, Gerald SJ, 1953; PALP 6/54
  - The Simple Rite of the Restored Order of Holy Week / by Ellard, Gerald SJ and F. P. Prucha SJ, 1958; PALP 7/01
  - The Catholic As Citizen and Apostle / by Elliott, Walter CSP, 1915; PALP 7/02
  - Eternal Punishment / by Elliott, Walter CSP, PALP 7/03
  - The Mystery of Suffering / by Elliott, Walter CSP, PALP 7/04
  - Novena to the Holy Ghost / by Elliott, Walter CSP, 1922; PALP 7/05
  - Jesus Christ is God / by Elliott, Walter Rev., PALP 7/06
  - The Ethics of War / by Emanuel, Cyprian OFM and the Committee on Ethics, 1932; PALP 7/07
  - The Morality of Conscientious Objection to War / by Emanuel, Cyprian OFM, 1941; PALP 7/08
  - Eastern Catholics / by Englert, Clement C. CSSR, 1940; PALP 7/09
  - Ephemerides Liturgicae / by Edizioni Liturgiche - Roma, 1951; PALP 7/10
  - The Reformation / by Evennett, H. O., 1950; PALP 7/11
  - Human Evolution - 1956 - Appendix: Present Catholic Attitude Towards Evolution / by Ewing, Franklin SJ, PALP 7/12
  - Catholic Defensive and Progressive Organisation / by Eyre, Edward KCSG, 1920; PALP 7/13
  - Purgatory / by Faber, Frederick William DD Rev, 1928; PALP 7/14
  - The Mass of the Roman Rite / by Farrell, H. J. CSSP, 1931; PALP 7/15
  - Holy Communion / by Fearon, John OP, 1959; PALP 7/16
  - The Federal Farm Board - Catholic Rural Life / by Schilling, W. F., 1929; PALP 7/17
  - Secularism Life without God / by Fee, John D. Rev, 1947; PALP 7/18
  - Communism Today or Red Fascism / by Feely, Raymond T. SJ, 1945; PALP 7/19
  - Communism and Morals / by Feely, Raymond T. SJ, 1935; PALP 7/20
  - The Church and the Jews / by Feige, Gregory - The Catholic Association for International Peace, 1937; PALP 7/21
  - The Defenders of the Faith / by Felix, Richard OSB, c1937; PALP 7/22
  - What is the Catholic Church? / by Felix, Richard OSB, 1922; PALP 7/23
  - The Catholic Mind v.XXXIX / by Fenn, Lyman A. SS, 1941; PALP 7/24
  - Vocations to the Priesthood / by Feen, Lyman A SS DD, 1938; PALP 7/25
  - Arbitration and the World Court / by Fenwick, Charles G. - International Law and Organization Committee, 1937; PALP 7/26
  - A Primer of Peace / by Fenwick, Charles G. - Catholic Association for International Peace, 1937; PALP 7/27
  - Crisis in the Catholic Schools / by Ferrer, Terry, 1961; PALP 7/28
  - Introduction to Catholic Action / by Ferree, William SM, PALP 7/29
  - Introduction to Social Justice / by Ferree, William SM, 1947; PALP 7/30
  - What's Wrong with the Sit-down Strike? / by Fichter, Joseph H. SJ, 1937; PALP 7/31
  - Questions People Ask about St. Joseph? / by Filas, Francis SJ, 1954; PALP 7/32
  - The Man Whom God Forgot / by Filas, Francis L., 1953; PALP 7/33
  - The Church and her Marriage Laws / by Finlay, Peter SJ, 1922; PALP 7/34
  - The One True Church: Which is It? / by Finlay, P. SJ., 1925; PALP 7/35
  - Was Christ God? / by Finlay, Peter SJ, 1929; PALP 7/36
  - Penance / by Finn, Thomas CSP, 1962; PALP 7/37
  - Stories of the Saints for Little People / by Finn, Agnes, 1939; PALP 7/38
  - Popular Indulgences Explained / by Finn, Daniel SJ, 1927; PALP 7/39
  - Christmas Stories No. 8 / by Finn, Francis SJ and Jessie Shalloe Waterman, PALP 7/40
  - The Christian / by Fitzsimons, John, 1950; PALP 7/41
  - The Mass - in the Early Church and Communion / by Pierse, Garrett DD and Flanagan Canon PP, 1931; PALP 7/42
  - The Eucharist / by Flanagan Neal M. OSM, 1962; PALP 7/43
  - An Elementary Catholic Catechism on the Morality of Segregation and Racial Discrimination / by Fletcher, Albert L., PALP 7/44
  - VIII. Christian Feminism a Charter of Rights and Duties - Catholic Studies in Social Reform / by Fletcher, Margaret, 1915; PALP 7/45
  - Catholicism Americanism and Communism / by Flynn, Fabian CP, 1937; PALP 7/46
  - Examination of Conscience for Teen-age and Up / by Flynn, Paul F. STB, 1949; PALP 7/47
  - The People's Mass - Chants and Prayers / by Foley, Joseph R CSP, 1959; PALP 7/48
  - Brief Catechism of Catholic Action / by Fontenelle, R. Msgr. - Round Table Conference of Catholic Action, 1955; PALP 7/49
  - Catholic Action / by Fontenelle, R. Msgr., O'Duffy P. J. and P. P. MacInerney, Translators, 1933; PALP 7/50
  - May Catholics be Psychoanalyzed? / by Ford, John C. SJ, 1954; PALP 7/51
  - The Book of Proverbs / by Forestell, Terence J. CSB, 1960; PALP 7/52
  - The Complete Exposure of Russion Communism / by Forrest, M. D. MSC, 1949; PALP 7/53
  - Consecration of the Family to the Sacred Heart / by Forrest, M. D. MSC, PALP 7/54
  - The Ideal Friendship / by Forrest, M. D. MSC, PALP 7/55
  - Nightmare of Infallible Fallacies / by Forrest, Michael D. MSC, 1954; PALP 7/56
  - Priestly Ministration to the Dying / by Forrest, Michael D. MSC, 1951; PALP 7/57
  - The Rosary / by Forrest, M. D. Rev, 1926; PALP 7/58
  - Who is the Pope? / by Forrest, M. D. MSC, 1931; PALP 7/59
  - Why are Anglican (Episcopalian) Orders Invalid? / by Forrest, M. D. MSC, 1947; PALP 7/60
  - Why Not be a Catholic? / by Forrest, M. D. MSC, PALP 7/61
  - The Vestments of the Roman Rite / by Fortescue, Adrian, PALP 7/62
  - Canon Law the Pope and the People / by Fox, Samuel F. Darwin, PALP 7/63
  - For People who Never Made a Retreat / by Finnegan, E. CSSR, PALP 7/64
  - God's Mercy / by Fischer SVD, 1957; PALP 7/65
  - The Sacrament of Confirmation / by Fisher, Ralph CSC, 1961; PALP 7/66
  - Tell My Fortune / by Fitzgerald, Daniel L., 1931; PALP 7/67
  - The Christian in a Changing World / by Fitzsimons, John, 1950; PALP 7/68
  - The Parish Priests Examen / by Franz, John B. DD, 1955; PALP 7/69
  - A Catholic Invitation to one Not of our Faith / by Frassrand, Michael X. CSP, 1947; PALP 7/70
  - Sinners and Saints / by Frassrand, Michael CSP, 1937; PALP 7/71
  - These Human Ills / by Frassrand, Michael X. CSP, 1933; PALP 7/72
  - The Holy Eucharist / by Freeland, Canon Msgr., 1926; PALP 7/73
  - The Head of the Family - Husband and Father: Rights and Obligations Ordained by God / by Frenay, Adolph Dominic OP, 1935; PALP 7/74
  - Is Life Worth Living? / by Frenay, Adolph Dominic OP, 1933; PALP 7/75
  - Tips on Temptation / by Fulkerson, Benjamin R. SJ, 1933; PALP 7/76
  - How to go to Hell / by Furfey, Paul Hanly, PALP 7/77
  - Grail Review v. V No. 1 / by The Grail International Secretariate, 1963; PALP 7/78
  - The Dawning of Emancipation 1791 to 1821 / by Gwynn, Denis, 1929; PALP 7/79
  - Homiletic Service v. 2 No. 8 / by The Catholic Centre - University of Ottawa, 1963; PALP 7/80
  - Recovery, Inc. An Answer to Nervous Problems - An Interview with John J. Higgins SJ / by Duggan, Martin L., 1955; PALP 7/81; Subject: A Self-Help, Family and Community Program
  - The Daily Examen / by Imbs, Charles A. SJ, 1935; PALP 8/01
  - Information - The Catholic Church in American Life / by Missionary Society of St. Paul the Apostle in N.Y. (Magazine), 1956; PALP 8/02
  - Everyday Ecumenism - Your New Relationship with Your Non-Catholic Neighbors / by Jacobs, William J., 1965; PALP 8/03
  - The New Mass / by Jacobs, William J., 1965; PALP 8/04
  - The Immaculate Conception / by Jaggar, J. B. SJ, 1925; PALP 8/05
  - Anglicanism / by Janssens, A. J. Rev, PALP 8/06
  - I am a Catholic because I am a Jew / by Angress, Hugh Israelowicz - Jarrett, Bede OP, 1921; PALP 8/07
  - 1962 Christmas Message / by Pope John XXIII, PALP 8/08
  - Mater et Magistra - Christianity and Social Progress / by Pope John XXIII, 1961; PALP 8/09
  - Hinduism / by Johanns, P SJ, 1948; PALP 8/10
  - Contribution of Catholic Education to American Life / by Johnson, George Rev, PALP 8/11